Email:

joedkirkup@gmail.com

Joe Kirkup

joekirkup.me

Mobile:

07504 610921

### **Personal Profile**

I am currently an undergraduate Computer Science student at Sheffield Hallam University, using my strong affinity for mathematical and logical problems, demonstrated by my A in maths and B in further maths, to stand out from my peers when solving class and assignment-based propositional issues. I can communicate well with peers thanks to my experience with customer support and communications at Team Knowhow and first line support at St Barnabas Hospice.

## **Education**

2019 – Current Sheffield Hallam University

BSc Computer Science – BCS Accredited Qualification including:

- Programming for Computer Science
- Mathematics for Computer Science
- Algorithms and Data Structures
- Computer Architecture
- Systems Modelling
- Professional Experience and Project Development

2017 – 2019 <u>Lincoln College</u>

Level 3 Extended Diploma in Computing; Achieved Grade ???

2014 – 2016 <u>Lincoln UTC</u>

10 GCSEs A-C including A in Computer Science and Maths, B in

**Further Maths** 

# **Experience**

# <u>Sept 2019 - St Barnabas Hospice – IT Administrator and Technician</u>

Assisted in general administration of the IMT department and maintenance of company networks, helped configure and deploy new and reused company laptop and desktop computers.

Worked alongside second-line support technician to troubleshoot and provide quick responses and solutions to IT related issues throughout the organisation, across numerous sites.

Researched, developed, tested and documented a formal process for efficiently imaging and reimaging machines whilst providing first line support to company employees and contractors.

Nov 2018 – Jun 2019 - Team Knowhow – Laptop Repair Admin at Newark Repair Centre Worked under loose supervision to diagnose and remedy hardware and software faults with customer laptops.

Communicated with customers to ascertain further details regarding the fault if necessary, providing coherent and respectful explanations to the customer about any perceived (but not actual) faults.

Ensuring the safety of any devices returned to the customer whether in a repaired or unrepaired state (notably charging devices or laptops with charging/power related faults).

#### References

Character

Rachel Varley – Family friend, 15+ years
Base Lockwood Lettings and Management,

453 High Street,

Lincoln, LN5 8JA

Tel: 01522 842550

Email: info@baseletting.co.uk

### Professional

Tom Bruton – IMT Department Leader at St Barnabas Hospice

IM&T Department Leader, St Barnabas Hospice

Hawthorn Road,

Lincoln LN2 4QX

Tel: 07549 029876

Email: tom.bruton@stbarnabashospice.co.uk

Steven Colson - IMT Technician at St Barnabas Hospice

IM&T Department, St Barnabas Hospice

Hawthorn Road,

Lincoln LN2 4QX

Tel: 07851 447037

Email: <u>steven.colson@stbarnabashospice.co.uk</u>

Mike Meredith - Course Leader at Sheffield Hallam University

Cantor Building, Room 9321, Sheffield Hallam University

153 Arundel St,

Sheffield S1 2NU

Tel: 0114 225 6908

Email: m.meredith@shu.ac.uk

<u>Dan Dolby – Manager at Team Knowhow</u>

Student Liaison Manager, Team Knowhow

Long Hollow Way, Coddington, Newark

NG24 2NH

Tel: 07413 423841

Email: dan.dolby@dixonscarphone.com